Are you sure it's this way, Keiji?
Don't underestimate my nose,
Elizabeth.
There's also a scent of
another animal mixed in...
If we mess up,
Piyoko might already be...!
Help me... Mister!
EPISODE 4
HOMING IN ON DESIRE
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go!
Hold it, cat burglar!
Give us that chick back, calmly.
M-Mister!
This is my prey!
I'll never hand it over!
Then a fight it is...
Mama!
Mama...
I told you not to leave the house!
- We're hungry!
- I'm starving, Mama!
Did you take Piyoko...
for your children?
I haven't been able to give
my children a proper meal
over the last 10 days...
If you'd like...
I have a little bit of food...
What?
It's a nutritious freshly laid egg!
I was just about to lay one.
Wow!
What is this?
- It looks tasty!
- It smells good!
Don't worry, please eat it.
It's an unfertilized egg,
so it's not alive.
- Thank you!
- So delicious!
Well, I'll be able to lay one too,
one of these days.
I don't know how I can thank you!
I can't eat them myself,
so I usually have to
throw them away.
I'm glad it didn't go to waste.
But... you're a domesticated cat, right?
Your owner doesn't feed you?
Well... that's...
Hey Elizabeth, look.
W-What are those holes?
Everyone's digging!
Women...
Even the elderly!
They don't seem to be
in their right minds.
That's my owner.
What?
What is going on?!
I-I'm scared!
It's that monster's fault.
"Monster"?
It showed up 10 days ago...
I don't know what it's motives are,
but it's making the villagers
dig holes without sleep or rest.
It's living in a mansion on
the outskirts of the village.
I feel so bad for
the children of the village.
They're confined to a shed.
And they aren't being fed properly.
I'm so sorry this happened.
This isn't your fault, Sei!
But we can't take this anymore.
If this keeps up,
we'll actually die.
We have nothing left to lose.
Listen, we have to push
with all our strength.
Okay.
Ready, set...
There was a noise coming
from over there...
I'll hold this guy here,
get out of here!
B-But...
I'm not leaving you, Sei!
Don't be stupid!
They'll kill you if they catch you!
I'll catch up!
Just go!
Don't move!
Sei...
I'll shoot anyone
who tries to escape!
Oh, how amazing!
Chickens?
PROCESSING INPUT
Those two are just passed out.
I'd appreciate it
if you could tie them up
with rope or something
before they wake up.
What? You're kidding!
What's up with these chickens?
It's using a smartphone...
Amazing,
it's a genius chicken!
What an amazing machine...
it can speak human...
Hurry, Sei!
O-okay...
I'm coming!
Let's go to my house for now!
Okay!
Ms. Cat,
thanks for guiding us!
Not at all, I'm happy to help!
It's hard for us chickens
to see clearly at night.
Have you dealt with them?
Probably...
they were the only guards in town.
Have the police or anyone come
to help you at any point?
I have a feeling the officer
possessed by the monster
did a good job
keeping everything under wraps.
Seems this monster is cunning.
Found it!
CHICKEN MISO RAMEN
It smells so good!
You're amazing, Sei.
I'm kinda surprised...
...that there are chickens
in this world that can talk.
- It's done!
- Yay!
- Thanks for the food!
Wow! So good!
I'm so full!
You're seem like you're
used to cooking.
My mom died when I was little,
so I just happened to
get good at it.
I see...
We're currently on a journey
to defeat the Demons
appearing across Japan.
The monster that appeared here
may be a Demon.
I know it's hard seeing your family
be possessed,
but could you tell us anything
about the monster?
We've been locked up
this entire time,
so we don't know much.
I see...
Hey Keiji,
why don't we go pay a visit
to this monster's mansion tomorrow?
Ask how many horns
this monster has...
Does it have four?
Does this monster have any horns?
Uh, no.
I don't think it had that many,
Then I'll pass.
What did you say?!
I only want to settle things
with that bastard.
I could care less about
Demons that have nothing to do with me.
All these people are suffering!
Don't you feel anything for them?
Nope.
You're horrible!
I misjudged you!
Oh no... this is the worst timing!
He's coming!
Not now, this is not the time!
His Highness has arrived!
The Lord of the Rut has arrived!
This extra potent natural urge
only hits me once or twice a year!
I want to do it.
I can't take it anymore!
I want to do it... I want to do it!!
Pardon me...
What?!
What are you doing, you pervert?!
Elizabeth,
you're the only one who can
calm the call of
The Lord of the Rut!
So, please!
You're not making any sense!
It's just your instincts again!
What are the chickens doing?
You think they're okay?
What is it?
I can't see!
Fine.
If you help me take care
of the Demon tomorrow,
I'll give you
what you want.
Really?!
Wait, but does that mean
I have to wait until tomorrow?
Yes.
O-Okay.
Tomorrow it is then. For sure.
He's that desperate?
So scary!
It's my duty...
You're dangerous.
Go sleep in the bathroom.
Sei?!
I couldn't sleep a wink.
Never mind that!
Sei's gone!
What happened?
Do you know where Sei went?
You don't think
he went to go see the monster—
Don't!
What do you mean?
Well, um...
Who's there?
Please tell me...
Why did Sei go to
the monster's mansion?
Um, that monster is...
...Sei's father.
Please help him!
Sei is going to get killed!
Show me where this monster is...
Did you come here
to get eaten, kid?
G-Give me back my dad!
You've got
a neat toy with you.
- Give me back my dad!
- Shut up!
D-Dad!
Dad, I'm begging you!
Please stop this!
Sei, hold on for
just a little bit longer...
just a little bit...
and Dad's dreams will come true.
Go! Go, go!
That's it! Looking good.
Let's go 3-6!
Damn it!
I was so close to winning big!
Dad, you borrowed more money,
didn't you?
Yeah, I did.
But I lost it all at the track.
Are you kidding me?!
That's over 5 million!
Do you even have a plan
to pay all of that back?!
Of course I have a plan, Sei!
I'm having someone introduce me
to an underground casino.
I'm gonna win big there,
pay off all of my debts...
and with the money
I have left over,
I'm gonna start my own business.
Then I'll buy us a mansion
with a pool!
Why don't you stop dreaming
and just get a job?
Idiot! No one gets rich
just working at a regular job!
That brat Sei...
Who does he think he is?
I'm not giving up now.
One day, I'm gonna get money
and make it big.
Oh?
Ow...
What is this?
When I dug it up,
There were some old coins
and a scroll inside.
I studied and decoded
the text myself.
It claimed...
A long time ago,
bandits buried their loot of
10,000 ryo somewhere in this area.
Today, that's worth over
1 billion yen.
God's finally on my side!
I'm gonna be rich!
That's when I started digging like
a man possessed by something.
- You're causing trouble!
- Get a hold of yourself, Dai!
- Stop it!
- Give it a rest!
Don't you feel bad for your kid?!
My buried treasure!
- I dug for a year straight,
- It has to be here!
- but I couldn't find any treasure.
- I know it is!
Where's my money?
Dad, please stop!
My, my, my...
My money!!
Dad!
Please stop already, Dad.
Sei, you want to
be rich too, right?
If we were rich,
we could leave this village.
You'd get all the toys
and snacks you want—
I don't want any of that!
I just want to live a normal life
with you, Dad.
I don't want a lot of money!
I understand.
Hey monster...
Zip me up.
Hey brat, what the hell
are you talking about?
Money's the answer!
Money is everything!
I want money.
Money!
Give me money!
Money... money!
I want money!!
Money!
I was right.
A Demon variant.
But I wasn't expecting a giant.
You guys!
Huh? Chickens?
Hey jerk, is "money"
the only word you know?
It really makes my crown curl!
Livestock challenging me
to a fight?
How fun.
Keiji!
Don't look at that!
I knew it!
That's how the villagers were—!
If you want the buried treasure
so much, dig it up yourself!
Don't make others do
your dirty work, you filth!
Shut up, you annoying fly!
How dare you call a lady a fly!
Money...
Did you just do something?
Guess I need more voltage.
I'm the one you're fighting!
No matter where you attack me from,
I'll devour you.
Although, I'd rather devour money...
I see how it is.
Oh, they're supposed to be
zippers on a wallet.
I finally get it now...
In that case...
Take this!
Kokekokko!
He's fast!
What?!
Nice attack.
But it doesn't do anything
if you can't hit anything.
Money...
This guy's a pain...
Mr. Rooster!
Please!
Don't kill my dad!
That's it!
Keiji, lure the Demon over there.
Got it!
Stop it!
Come back here!
Keiji, stop him here!
Got it.
Stay still, you fly!
I'll start by eating you first!
Th-These are...!
No way!
This is the only way
to take down the Demon
without killing Sei's father.
If that wasn't enough,
here's more voltage.
T-T-Treasure!
Your back's wide open!
M-My body...
Keiji, now!
Got it!
Take this!
Kokekokko!
Money!
What?
What am I doing here?
What was I doing?
Digging holes?
Oh, she's awake!
Why does my mouth taste like dirt?
Elizabeth!
If you help me take care of
the Demon...
I'll give you
what you want.
Y-Your promise!
Huh?
What?
Did you forget?
I have a long-standing grudge
against you.
I'm not doing anything with you!
Dad!
S-Sei...
H-H-Help me!
I was forced to fight and I didn't
even get anything out of it.
This is all your fault.
Nothing good comes out of leaving
a greedy bastard like you alive.
Die!
Stop!
Don't get in my way, brat!
I'm not gonna hold back!
What are you doing, Keiji?!
Dad!
Keiji!
Sei, get out of here!
If you're gonna do it,
just kill me!
Dad!
I'm trash.
I'm a worthless human.
I've been a burden
to everyone in the village.
It's true,
maybe I do deserve to die.
But please...
Spare Sei.
Please don't kill Sei!
He's my precious, precious son!
Please!
Please don't kill my son!
D-Dad...
Please!
Please, Mr. Rooster!
I hope you remember this feeling
for as long as you live your life.
Sei, do your best.
O-Okay.
Be well.
Guess I'm the kind of guy
who gets scolded by chickens...
There's no way I'd make it big.
That was kind of impressive.
Well, if he doesn't straighten out
after that, then he's real trash.
Oh?
Maybe you're not as bad, after all.
I got a chance!
Of course.
Love conquers all.
Speaking of...
Elizabeth, I love you.
Who's the real...
...trash here?!
The Lord of the Rut...
...has left.
I might have gone too far.
Mister! Are you all right?!
Please get it together!
Are you all right, Mr. Rooster?
Don't overdo it.
I got some really insane
footage here...
This... is gonna go viral.
I can't take this anymore!
I'm done traveling with you two!
Also, what's a Demon doing
in a place like this?
Next time:
The Motley Flock Scatters
Each and every last one them makes my
crown curl!
FAN ART CONTEST AWARDS